<resources>
    <string name="app_name">E-Assistant</string>


    <!--******************************************************ARRAYS***********************************************************-->
    <array name="more_recycler_view_titles">
        <item>Log Out</item>
        <item>Directory</item>
        <item>Share</item>
        <item>Rate</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>About</item>
    </array>


    <array name="directory_agencies_names">
        <item>Office of Disaster Preparedness and Emergency Management (ODPEM)</item>
        <item>National Water Commission (NWC)</item>
        <item>National Works Agency (NWA)</item>
        <!--<item>Jamaica Public Service (JPS)</item>-->
        <!--<item>National Environment and Planning Agency (NEPA)</item>-->
    </array>

    <array name="directory_agencies_info">
        <item>
            ABOUT:\n
            The ODPEM has the unique role of being the only government agency to provide disaster
            management functions in Jamaica. Disaster preparedness is a dynamic function, which
            includes
            the identification of disaster threats and risks throughout the country and the
            formulation
            of plans to create a state of readiness to meet the needs of victims when a disaster
            strikes.\n\n

            ADDRESS: 2-4 Haining Rd, Kingston, Jamaica\n\n

            CONTACT:\n
            TELEPHONE: (876) 906-9674-5 or (876) 754-9077-8\n\n

            TOLL FREE: 1-888-2255-637\n\n

            EMAIL: odpem@cwjamaica.com\n\n

            WEBSITE: www.odpem.org.jm/\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            ABOUT:\n
            The NWC supplies 190 million gallons of potable water each day to its
            more than 400,000 registered accounts representing about 2 million persons across
            Jamaica. Within the last five decades, the growth of the industrial sector added
            to the establishment of several new residential communities in various sections of
            St. Andrew, St. Catherine and many other parishes across Jamaica, has led to the
            increased demand for potable water.\n\n

            ADDRESS:\n
            Corporate Office: 28 Barbados Avenue, Kingston 5\n

            For More Office Locations: http://www.nwcjamaica.com/Offices\n\n

            CONTACT:\n
            TOLL FREE: 1.888.CALL.NWC (1-888-225-5692)\n\n

            WEBSITE: http://www.nwcjamaica.com
        </item>

        <item>
            ABOUT:\n
            The National Works Agency is directly responsible for Jamaica\'s main road network,
            consisting of approximately 5000 km of class A, B and C roads. This network forms 19
            percent
            of the total road surface available to a nation which relies almost exclusively on
            roads,
            as the means of moving around the island. More than 90 percent of the main road network
            is paved.
            The NWA also has 736 bridges on its main road network.\n
            For More Info: http://www.nwa.gov.jm/history\n\n

            ADDRESS:\n
            140 Maxfield Avenue Kingston 10\n\n

            CONTACT:\n
            TELEPHONE: 1-876-926-3210-9\n
            DIGICEL: 1-876-618-ROAD(7623)/1-876-618-7623\n
            TOLL FREE: 1-888-429-5692\n\n

            WEBSITE: http://www.nwa.gov.jm
        </item>
    </array>
</resources>
